________________________________

Precisely Portal Texture Pack: 
a variation of my "Modified Portal" pack for those who want mushroom turrets and combustible lemons, etc.

by carlotta4th

________________________________

PERMISSIONS: You're welcome to modify the packs to fit your own needs/dungeons/etc, but you cannot make profit off of the textures themselves, claim the textures as your own, or post them without giving credit and linking back to the originals. Thank you!
Texture pack link: http://www.minecraftforum.net/topic/158542-16x-32x12-precisely-portal-and-modified-portal/#Index


CREDITS:
-The first portal texture pack for minecraft was "Portal meets Minecraft" by Cosine. THIS pack was the first Beta/survival mode Portal pack, and it is a continuation of Cosine's alpha pack (with permission).
-Restcoser (from the minecraft forums) for the "Lava "goo" animation.
-All unchanged 32x32 "vanilla minecraft" textures come from Vattic's "Faithful 32x32" as available here: http://www.minecraftforum.net/topic/72747-faithful-32x32-pack-updatectm-support-15/
-Minecraft is property of Mojang and Notch, Portal is property of Aperture Science and Valve Corporation. Respective credit is applied as such.

Directions to install the texture pack:
________________________________

Easy:
1. Open minecraft and click "Texture Packs."
2. "Open Texture Pack Folder"
3. Copy/Drag the Downloaded Folder in.

More involved:
1. Use your computers search function ("find" or "search") and type in "Run"
2. Open run and type: %appdata%/.minecraft/texturepacks
3. Drag the texture pack zip file into this folder
4. Open minecraft and click on "Mods and Texture Packs" in the main menu.
5. The pack should be there, enjoy!